Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/aliyasminrahaman-884827160 (LinkedIn) aliyasminrahaman.com (Blog)

Top Skills
SQL
C++
Testing

Aliyasmin Rahaman

Marketing Strategy Intern at CodeVector Labs - Al solutions | Summer Intern-Shell | MBA 19-21, IIFT | D&I Enthusiast Kolkata

Summary

I am currently pursuing MBA (IB) from the Indian Institute of Foreign Trade, batch of 2019-21. I am the Senior Club Co-ordinator(SCC) for IIFT K Toastmasters Club. I have worked with TCS as a System Engineer for 26 months. I have experience in Functional Testing and Accessibility Testing. I have completed my Initial Learning Program (ILP) from TCS, Trivandrum in MS.Net. I have pursued my graduation in Electronics and Communication Engineering from Meghnad Saha Institute Of Technology, West Bengal University of Technology.

Writing short stories is my hobby. I am one of the winners at 'Yes I Write' - corporate story writing competition organized by StoryMirror and Yes Bank. Read that story here: https://storymirror.com/read/story/english/t2jlcw4k/the-tale-of-the-wall

I also like listening to music. I am trained in Indian Classical Music. I like reading books. 'The Power of Your Sub-conscious Mind' is one of my favourite books.

Interacting to people from diverse cultures and backgrounds is what I am extremely passionate about!

Experience

CodeVector Labs - Al solutions Marketing Strategy Intern July 2020 - Present (2 months)

Shell Summer Intern April 2020 - May 2020 (2 months)

I worked with the Sales & Operations team to Strategize a Sustainable Diversity and Inclusion culture in the company operated retail outlets.

Page 1 of 2

TCS

System Engineer March 2017 - May 2019 (2 years 3 months)

Kolkata, West Bengal, India

I worked as a Functionality and Accessibility Tester. I have ISTQB certification which tests ones skills related tk Testing and Quality Assurance.

I was also involved in TCS Maitree Kolkata Toastmasters Club (CSR wing of TCS). I had served as Club Secretary for the tenure Jan - June, 2018.

Education

Indian Institute of Foreign Trade MBA IB, Management · (2019 - 2021)

West Bengal University of Technology, Kolkata

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Electrical, Electronics and Communications

Engineering · (2012 - 2016)

Jalpaiguri Govt. Girls' High School Higher Secondary, Science · (2010 - 2012)

Jalpaiguri Govt. Girls' High School Secondary, General